33hops.com 2019-05-28

# 33HOPS | Privacy Policy

**What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our blog, website or app?**

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name, email address or other details to help you with your experience.

**When do we collect information?**

We collect information from you when you fill out a form or enter information on our site.

**How do we use your information?**

We may use the information we collect from you when you register, make a purchase, sign up for our newsletter, respond to a survey or marketing communication, surf the website, or use certain other site features in the following ways:

**•** To personalize user's experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.

 **•** To improve our website in order to better serve you.

 **•** To allow us to better service you in responding to your customer service requests.

 **•** To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.

 **•** To quickly process your transactions.

 **•** To ask for ratings and reviews of services or products

 **•** To follow up with them after correspondence (live chat, email or phone inquiries)

 **How do we protect visitor information?**

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security holes and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible. 

We do not collect credit card information.

We do not use Malware Scanning.

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. 

We implement a variety of security measures when a user places an order to maintain the safety of your personal information.

All transactions are processed through a gateway provider and are not stored or processed on our servers.

**Do we use 'cookies'?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site's or service provider's systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

**•** Help remember and process the items in the shopping cart.

**•** Understand and save user's preferences for future visits.

**•** Keep track of advertisements.

**•** Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser (like Internet Explorer) settings. Each browser is a little different, so look at your browser's Help menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.  

**If users disable cookies in their browser:**

If you disable cookies off, some features will be disabled It will turn off some of the features that make your site experience more efficient and some of our services will not function properly.

However, you can still place orders over the telephone .

**Third-party disclosure**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

 **Third-party links**

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third-party products or services on our website. These third-party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

 **Google**

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.  

**We have implemented the following:**

**•** Remarketing with Google AdSense

 **•** Google Display Network Impression Reporting

 **•** Demographics and Interests Reporting

 **•** DoubleClick Platform Integration  

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website. 

Opting out:  
Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising initiative opt out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**We collect your email address in order to:**

Communicate availability of new releases or new tools. Promote 33HOPS products, services or posts or from a third party. 

All collected information is covered by the [Spanish Organic Law for Data Protection (LOPD)](https://www.agpd.es/portalwebAGPD/canaldocumentacion/informes_juridicos/reglamento_lopd/index-ides-idphp.php)  
and registered at the [Spanish Data Protection Agency](https://www.agpd.es/)  
with registry number B835837160342016180042

**  
If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can** use our [contact form](http://33hops.com/formulario-de-contacto.asp) requesting so, and we will promptly remove you from **ALL** correspondence.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

33hops.com

Castilla la Mancha 95

San Sebastian de los Reyes, Madrid 28700 

Spain

info@33hops.com

+34916636085

Last Edited on 2016-03-31
